everydaydishes.com 2017-12-09

# privacy policy – Everyday Dishes

We are part of “CherylStyle, LLC.” Brands, which include Everyday Dishes, everydaydishes.com, and Live the Moment. CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands are committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of contact information you share with us (the phrase “contact information” means any information by which you can be contacted, such as your name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of, the information. By using any of our web sites or sharing your contact information with us, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.As a part of our commitment to your privacy, CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association’s “Privacy Promise to American Consumers.” We have agreed to (1) provide customers with notice of their ability to opt out of information rental, sale, or exchange with other marketers; (2) honor customers’ requests not to share their contact information with other marketers; and (3) honor customers’ requests not to receive mail, telephone, or other solicitations from CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands.

**Collecting Information About You**

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product, subscribe to a service, register to receive catalogs, sign up to receive emails, submit information and personal content on the Everyday Dishes website, or to participate in contests, sweepstakes or promotions, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain contact information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date, gender, occupation, personal interests, and other information. When providing information to Everyday Dishes, you are also opting in to receive email newsletters from Everyday Dishes. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.

Whether or not to provide such information is completely your own choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our web sites. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive marketing communications from us.

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any contact information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us and analyze this data for preferences, trends, and site usage statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

**Using Information About You**

We use your contact information for internal purposes only, such as:

  * Confirming and tracking your order, subscription, or registration;
  * Analyzing preferences, trends, and statistics;
  * Informing you of our new products, services, and offers, newsletters; and
  * Providing you with other information from and about CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands.

We process your contact information only in ways compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or authorized by you. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to make sure that your contact information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable with regard to its intended use.

From time to time we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy policies are consistent with ours. These are known as our Select Partners. In such cases we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross-reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online. We may also combine that information with publicly available information and information we receive from or cross-reference with our Select Partners and others. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and others with us, to communicate with you about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We call them our Service Providers. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our websites. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/>.

In certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.

**Opting Out Of Marketing And Transfers; Updating and Deleting Information About You**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from our Select Partners, or if you would like to opt out of our rental or exchange of your information with other marketers, please let us know. In the U.S., you can call us at 602-476-0630 or email us. Please be sure to include your full name, email address, mailing address, and specifically what information you do not want to receive. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address or other contact information with us please contact us the same way. If you like, you may use either of the following statements in your message to us:

  * “I prefer not to receive email advertisements, such as updates regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.”
  * “I prefer not to receive direct mail advertisements, such as periodic catalogs and mailings regarding products and services, special promotions or upcoming events.”

You may also click the designated link at the bottom of all email advertisements to be removed from future email updates.

Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take up to ten days for your email request and 6-8 weeks to process your postal mail request.

**Cookies**

When you visit our websites, we send one or more “cookies” to your computer or other device. We may also use cookies in emails that you receive from us. A “cookie” is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A “session cookie” expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A “persistent cookie” stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date the cookie information is still available. Generally, we use cookies to improve the quality of our service when you visit our website and other websites of interest to you. We also use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our websites and to process your order, track your status in our promotions, contests and sweepstakes, and/or analyze your visiting patterns.

Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. They are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Service Providers. However, we respect your right to choose whether to be included in such services. You may opt out of certain of these services by emailing us. In addition, in connection with the services that they provide to us, certain of our Service Providers may work with third parties who may use cookies to collect anonymous information to tailor advertising for you and others elsewhere on the Internet. These third parties do not have access to any contact information about you. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our websites or other services may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

**Security**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our websites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name and address so only we are able to decode your information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or Internet cafe.

**Protecting Children**

CherylStyle, LLC dba Everyday Dishes Brands take special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. Our websites are general audience sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.  
Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any contact information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children’s online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children’s access to the Internet.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Our websites may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked sites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked site before disclosing any of your information on such site.

**Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our websites, as applicable. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date posted in the notice and at the end of the revised Privacy Policy. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our websites and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our websites or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.

**Your Feedback**

To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. In the U.S., you can call us at 602-476-0630 or email us.
